- med.haouam@gmail.com
- A Ben arous, Ezzahra
- mate of birth 16/09/1993
- □ Tunisian
- +216 53 851 745

About me

I'm a full stack developer. Net Core and Angular with a 4 years experience in the web development and desktop applications, I worked on ERP and business management projects.

In my field I am a perfectionist, ambitious and serious.
I'm always trying to evolve.

Languages

Arabic	
French	
English	

Interests

Sport

Strength training, Football

Voyager

Asia (South Korea, Japan, Thailand)

Autre intérêt

Camping, Hiking

Mohamed Iskander Haouem

Full stack developer (Angular / .Net Core)

Work experience

Full stack developer

Since September 2020 Nerium Software Tunis

- Work on the **NextGC** project, management software for the horticulture and viticulture fields.
- Participate in the migration of the **Flowone / Vinistoria** project developed in Delphi to the new **NextGC** project with new technologies: ASP.NET CORE 3.1, Angular 8 to 12 and NHibernate.

Environment:

ASP.NET Core 3.1, C#, Nhibernate, Angular 8 to 12, TypeScript, SCSS, XML, SQL, Visual studio 2019, VSCode.

• Full stack developer

From February 2020 to August 2020 Bitbase Tunis

- Working on the **KAMEON** project, customer relationship management and corporate resource planning software.
- Participate in the migration of the main product KAMEON (CRM/ ERP)
 developed in ASP.NET web Forms towards the new technologies ASP.NET
 CORE 2.2 and Angular 7.

Environment:

ASP.NET Core 2.2, C#, IdentityServer, Angular 7, TypeScript, SCSS, MVC, XML, CQS architecture, Visual studio 2019, VSCode, Git, Bitbucket.

.Net Developer

From January 2019 to January 2020 TSI Tunis, Ariana

Work on the TSI ERP solution which consists of several modules such as:

- **Treasury**: module for managing all cash and bank operations.
- Pay: module for calculating pay stubs.
- **General accounting**: module that allows the management of accounting according to Tunisian standards.
- **HRM**: module to manage all aspects of HR (personal management, recruitment, careers, training, social assessment, etc.)
- **Commercial**: module allowing the management of all commercial aspects (quotation, order, delivery, invoice, payment)

Design and development of commercial software for **FARMASI** client

Environment:

.Net Framework, C#, Microsoft SQL Server 2014, WinForms, Visual Studio 2012.

Work experience

.Net Developer

From September 2017 to December 2018 AACMI Tunis

- Design and development of an AACMI-specific ERP application containing the following modules: Personnel Management, Member Management, Accounting Management, Magazine Management, etc..
- Creation and maintenance of a CMS blog with WordPress for AACMI activities.

Environment:

.Net Framework, C#, Microsoft SQL Server 2012, WinForms, Wordpress, Visual Studio 2012.

Education

Mastère Professionnel Spécialité : Ingénierie des applications Web-Nuagiques

From September 2019 to September 2021 UVT / ISET Kairouan Tunis, Kairouan

Licence Applique en Informatique Spécialité : Développement Système Informatique

From September 2012 to June 2017 ISET Charguia Tunis, Ariana

Baccalaureate in Computer Science

June 2012 Lycée Ibn Rachik Ben Arous, Ezzahra

Skills

Programming languages

HTML, XML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, C#

os

Windows, Linux

VSC

Git, TFS, SVN, Github, Bitbucket, TortoiseSVN

Libraries

Bootstrap, JQuery

Framework

Angular

Tools

SourceTree, Jira, Projeqtor, Zoho

SGBD

SQL Server, Oracle Database

Nosql

Mongodb, Neo4j